Guide to the Guide to the Civil Service Technical Guild Records WAG.024
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VIII: General Files
  - Assignment Differential, 1968-1969, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Assignment Differential, 1981-1984 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Assignment Differential, 1985-1990 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Awards and Honors, 1956-1965 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Benefit Fund Trust, Feb 1982 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Benefits, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Benefits, 1969-1983 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Black History Committee, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Board of Education: Article 78, Assistant Area Managers, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Board of Education: Budget Reports and Recommendations, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Board of Education: Certification for Telecommunications Title, 1987-1990 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Board of Education: Certification for Telecommunications Title, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Board of Education: Chapter 14, 1961-1966 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Board of Education: Chapter 14, 1974-1978 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Board of Education: Chapter 14, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Board of Education: Chapter 14, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Board of Education: Coalition, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Board of Education: Comptroller Audits on School Construction, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Board of Education: Contract, Jan 1979- Dec 1980 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Board of Education: Contract, Jan 1981- Dec 1982 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Board of Education: Contracting In, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Board of Education: Contracting Out, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Board of Education: Contracting Out, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Board of Education: Contracting Out, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Board of Education: Contracting Out, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Board of Education: Contracting Out, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Board of Education: Division of School Buildings, 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Board of Education: Farming Out, 1958-1980 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Board of Education: Illegal Appointments, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Board of Education: Inspection of School Buildings, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Board of Education: Needs Analysis, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Board of Education: Privatization, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Board of Education: Privatization, 1972-1975 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Board of Education: Privatization, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Board of Education: School Construction Authority, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Board of Education: School Construction Authority, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Board of Education: Telephone Work; TV Antenna, 1984-1988 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Board of Education: Transition Committee, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Board of Education Working Conditions Contract, 1961-1978 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Board of Estimate, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Board of Water Supply, 1945, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Broadbanding, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - "Building Education and The Building Crisis", 1986 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Cartoons by Hoop on Mayor Robert F. Wagner from The Chief, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Certification Arbitration, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Certification Arbitration, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Certification Arbitration, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Certification Arbitration, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Citizens Advisory Committee on LaGuardia Airport Subway Access, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Citizens Conference on Campaign Reform and Ethics in Government, May 1986 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - City Corps of Engineers, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - City Council Legislation, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - City Council Legislation, 1983, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - City Council Legislation, 1995, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - City Planning, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - CUNY Conference, "The Wages of Cybernation", Mar 1995 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Civil Service, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Civil Service Employees Association, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Civil Service Forum, 1937-1940 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Civil Service Forum, 1941-1945 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Civil Service Forum, 1946-1949 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Civil Service Forum, 1950-1954 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Civil Service Job Classifications, 1939-1940 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Civil Service Law, 1952, 1971-1974, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Civil Service Merit Council, 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Civil Service Retired Employees Association, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Coalition for a Safe Subway, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Committee for a More Responsive Union, 1978-1980, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Committee for Real Change, May 1999 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Comptroller, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Comptroller, Dec 1990 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Contract: City Wide, 1973-1976 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Contract: City Wide, 1990-1992, 1995-2000 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Contracting Out (I), 1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Contracting Out (II), 1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Contracting Out, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Contracting Out, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Cost of Living Adjustments (COLA), 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - COLA, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Council on Transportation, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Department for Professional Employees, AFL-CIO, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Department for Professional Employees, AFL-CIO, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Department of Environmental Protection, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Department of Environmental Protection, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Department of Health, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Department of Health, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Department of Housing, Preservation and Development, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Department of Housing, Preservation and Development, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Department of Personnel, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Department of Personnel, 1988-1990 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Department of Personnel, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Department of Personnel, 1992-1994 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Department of Personnel, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Diana, Raymond E.: Testimonial Certificate, Oct 1957 (Box MSXOS002, Folder 1)
  - Dinner Dance Programs, 1939-1982 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Disaffiliation (DC 37), 1978-1981 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Disaffiliation Committee, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Disaffiliation Committee, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - District Council 37 (DC 37): Administrator, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - DC 37 Fortieth Anniversary Booklet, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - DC 37 Hearings on Telecom, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - DC 37 Professional Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - DC 37 Professional Committee, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - DC 37 Professional Committee, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - DC 37 Professional Committee, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - DC 37 Professional Committee, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - DC 37 Professional Committee, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - DC 37 Professional Committee, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - DC 37 Professional Committee, 1988-1990 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - DC 37 Professional Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - DC 37 Professional Committee, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - DC 37 Professional Committee, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - DC 37 Professional Committee, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - DC 37 Professional Committee, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - DC 37 Professional Committee, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - DC 37 Professional Committee, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - DC 37 Professional Committee, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - DC 37 Save the Statue of Liberty Committee, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - DC 37 Standard Language Contracts, 1982-1984, 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Education Fund, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Education Programs, 1971-1976, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Empire State Transportation Alliance (ESTA), 2000 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Employment, 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Employment, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Engineers Administrative, 1970-1991 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Engineers Title Changes, 1940-1957 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Ethics in Government Act of 1987, 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Fair Share Committee, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Farming Out, 1941-1978 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Farming Out, 1979-1985 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Fashion Institute of Technology, 1978-1983 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Fire Department (Chapter 21), 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Fundraising, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Graphic Artists for Equity Fund, Jun 1984 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Grievance Representatives to DC 37, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Grievance Seminar, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Griffenhagen Report on Career and Salary Plans, 1951-1952 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Griffenhagen Survey, 1951-1953 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Gun Hill Bus Depot Project, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (Chapter 3), 1966-1969, 1974-1978 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (Chapter 3), 1979-1984 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Highway Department (Chapter 37), 1976-1980 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Highway Transportation Specialists, 1983-1985 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - History: Guild, 1957-1967 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - History: Guild, 1979, 1987, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Housing Authority (Chapter 25), 1973-1976 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Housing Authority (Chapter 25), 1983, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Howard, Alan, 1991-1995 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Indian Civil Service Employees Association, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Infrastructure, 1990-2000 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Installation Dinners, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Insurance Policies, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Intermodal Surface Transportation Efficiency Act (ISTEA), 1997 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Intermodal Surface Transportation Efficiency Act (ISTEA), 1998 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - ISTEA Works NY Coalition, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Italian-American Committee, Oct 1999 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Italian-American Committee, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Italian-American Labor Council, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Jobless Future Seminar, Mar 1995 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Labor Research Association, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Labor Research Association, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Landmarks Preservation Commission (Chapter 41), 1980 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Leadership Conference, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Leadership Conference, Sep 1992 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Leadership Conference, Oct 1992 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Leadership Conference, Jul 1993 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Leadership Conference, Oct 1993 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Leadership Conference, Aug 1994 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Leadership Conference, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Leadership Conference, Aug 1997 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Lobbying, 1938-1942 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Lobbying, 1943-1978 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Lobbying, 1980-1982 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Local 375: A911" Vests and Logo, undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Local 375: Corruption Charges, Jan 2003-Sep 2003 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Local Law 35: Efforts to Change (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Medical Complaint Journal, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Membership, 1973, 1983, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Membership, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Metropolitan Transportation Authority (MTA) Board Meeting Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - MTA Coalition, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - MTA Coalition, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - MTA Coalition, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - MTA Coalition, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - MTA Coalition, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - MTA Coalition, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - MTA Coalition, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - MTA Coalition, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - MTA Coalition, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - MTA Employment, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - MTA Inspector General, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - MTA Joint Campaign, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - MTA Legislative Meeting, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - MTA Lobby Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Minimum Salary Arbitration, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Moberg, Peggy, "Privatizing Government", 1994 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Municipal Coalition Economic Agreement, 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Municipal Engineers Forum, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Municipal Engineers Journal, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Municipal Engineers Journal, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Municipal Labor Committee (MLC), Civil Service Practice Committee (CSPC), 1988 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - MLC, CSPC, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - MLC, CSPC, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - MLC, CSPC, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - MLC, CSPC, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - MLC, CSPC, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - MLC, CSPC, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - MLC, CSPC, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - MLC, CSPC, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - MLC, CSPC, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - MLC, CSPC, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - MLC, CSPC, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - MLC Comptroller Meeting, Apr 1995 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - MLC Conference, Sep 1986 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - MLC Conference, Oct 1995-Nov 1995 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - MLC Conference, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - MLC Issues, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - MLC Privatization Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - MLC Privatization Committee, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - MLC Privatization Manual, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - MLC Steering and General Membership (I), 1995 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - MLC Steering and General Membership (II), 1995 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - MLC Steering and General Membership (III), 1995 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - MLC Steering and General Membership, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - MLC Steering and General Membership, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - MLC, Subcommittee to Revise Rules of Office of Collective Bargaining, 1987-1992 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - MLC, Tax Policy Committee, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - MLC, Tax Policy Committee, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - MLC, Tax Policy Committee, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Municipal Union Financial Leaders, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - National Society of Professional Engineers, 1941, 1989, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - National Society of Professional Engineers, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - National Society of Professional Engineers, 1998, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - New York Building Congress, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - New York Building Congress, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - New York Building Congress, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - New York City Central Labor Council, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - New York City Central Labor Council, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - New York City Educational Construction Fund, 1981, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - New York Metropolitan Transportation Council, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - New York Metropolitan Transportation Council, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - New York Metropolitan Transportation Council, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - New York State AFL-CIO, Transportation Division, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - New York State AFL-CIO, Transportation Division, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - New York State Civil Service Commission, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - New York State Senate Committee on Investigation, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - New York State Senate Committee on Transportation, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - New York State Society of Professional Engineers, 1985-1991 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - New York State Society of Professional Engineers: Guide for Employed Engineers, 1994-2000 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - New York Task Force for Port, Rail, and Industrial Development, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Pension Plan, 1978, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Pillar of Labor: Raymond Diana, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Police Headquarters Building and Plaza, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Political Activities; Affiliations, 1946, 1984, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Political Endorsements, 1949-1974 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Press Releases, 1958-1959, 1974-1982 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Privatization, 1984-1994 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Privatization, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Professional Development Committee, 1979-1988 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Professional Development Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Professional Technical Division Conference, 1970-1996 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Program Planners, Inc.: Contracting Out, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Promotion Examination for Assistant Mechanical Engineer, Feb 1956 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Publicity, 1946, 1986, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Public Service International (PSI), 1991 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Public Service International (PSI), 1992 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Public Service International (PSI), 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Public Works Historical Society, 1976-1984 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Quality of Work Life Programs, 1989-1991 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Rebuild America Campaign, 1992-1997 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Reclassification of Job Titles, 1984-1989, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Recruitment and Retention Planning Report, 1983-1991 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - "Redesigning NYC Engineering Infrastructure", Aug 1992 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Regional Plan Association, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Regional Plan Association, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Regional Plan Association, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Regional Plan Association, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Resignations (B. Mariano, P. Gagliarchi, and Harvey K. Friedland), 1981 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Resolution Against War on Iraq, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Retirement Dinner: Philip F. Brueck, Oct 1962 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Salary and Working Conditions, 1941-1948 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Salary and Working Conditions, 1952-1970 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Salary and Working Conditions, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Salary Review Panel, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Salary Review Panel, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Scholarship, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - School Asbestos Crisis, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - School Building Design, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - School Construction, 1986-1988 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - School Construction Authority (SCA) Legislation, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - SCA Recommendations, 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - SCA, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - SCA, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - SCA, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - SCA, 1997-1999 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Society of Architects and Engineers, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Straphangers Campaign, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Task Force on Capital Financing and Construction, 1987-1988, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Tax Exemption, 1951-1952 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Technicians Title Change Surveys, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Telecommunications (on DC 37 not providing services), 1986, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Telecommunications, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Telecommunications (Henry Mahler letter), 1992 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Telecommunications, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Telecommunications, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Telecommunications, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Telecommunications, 1995-1999 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Total Quality Management, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Traffic Control Inspectors, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Traffic Control Inspectors, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Transit Authority, 1939-1958 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Transit Authority, 1975-1977 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Transit Authority, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Transit Authority, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Transit Authority, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Transit Authority, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Transit Authority, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Transit Authority, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Transit Authority, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Transit Authority, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Transit Authority, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Transit Authority, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Transit Authority, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Transit Authority, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Transit Authority, 1989-1991 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Travel Club, 1970-1997 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Tri State Transit System, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Trustee Trust Funds, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Unauthorized removal of boxes, Apr 2003 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - United Farm Works of America, Oct 1996 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - United States Postal Permit, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Urban Mass Transportation Administration, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Urban Transportation Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Wagner Labor Archives, NYU, 1983-1988 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Wagner Labor Archives, NYU, 1997-2000 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Water Resources, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Weekly Allowances, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Wickes Law, 1981-1988 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Women=s Organizing Committee, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Workers= Compensation Board, 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - World Trade Center, Dec 2001 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Zetlin and De Chiara Lawyers Seminar, 1991, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Series IX: Newsletters, Bulletins and Clippings
  - American Institute of Architects Journal, 1944, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Civil Service Technical Guild Newsletter - The Guild Newsletters, 1974-2002 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Comptroller, Jan 1976 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - CPU, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Daily Noose, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Guild Tech-Quirer, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Informational Newsletter for Technical Employees, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Local 375 Newsletters, Aug 2002, Feb 2003 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - President's Report, 1974-1980 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Tech Guild News, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Technical Guild News, 1966-1977 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Technycian, 1937-1940 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Technycian, 1941-1945 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Technycian, 1946-1957 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Clippings, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1943-1948 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1952-1957 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1958-1960 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, 1968-1971 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Clippings, 1974-1976 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Clippings, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Clippings, 1981-1984 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Clippings, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Clippings, 1986-1989 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Clippings, 1990-1997 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Clippings, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Clippings, 2000-2002 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Series X: Women's Committee, 1985-2007
  - Attendence Sheets: Meetings, Jan 1994-Jan 2000 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Attendence Sheets: Meetings, Jun 1987-Dec 1993 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Budgets and Expenditures, 1986-1995 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Coalitions of Labor Union Women (CLUW), 1986-1993
  - Conferences Attended, 1985-1995 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence and Meetings, 1986-1997 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Demonstrations and Solidarity Actions, 1986-1997 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Events: Comparable Worth, Child Care, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Events: Guest Book, 1987-1991 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Events: Technical Women in the Workplace (Year 1), 1987 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Events: Our Mothers Ourselves (Year 2), 1988 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Events: Global Women (Year 3), 1989 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Events: The Balancing Act; Career and Family (Year 4), 1990 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Events: Women Changing Unions Changing (Year 5), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Events: Climbing Out-Rising Up (Year 6), 1992 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Events: Self-Defense Workshop, Nov 19, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Events: Women in the 90's-From Voters to Victors (Year 7), 1993 (Box 18, Folder 17)